- Previously
on "The Bachelor"...
- All right.
You ready for this?
- Yeah. I'm ready.
[cork pops]
Whoo!
- I heard a pop.
- What was that?
- You know what?
Hey.
I--I have to say something.
It's not okay what you did.
I brought this bottle
from Des Moines.
I said--
- I had no idea.
- [sighing]
Oh, my God.
That was supposed
to be my moment...
[sniffs]
and she took that from me.
I'm over you
trying to act like
you're Miss innocent,
because you're not.
- I'm not a champagne stealer.
- I'm over this, like,
pretty princess,
like, perfect [bleep].
- Like, I knew
it was gonna get real,
but I didn't know
it was gonna get like this.
- I was up all last night,
crying, and I felt bullied.
- She's trying to play
the victim card.
[sniffs]
It's just not--
it's not fair.
It sucks that she put
that word in his head.
The word "bully"
takes it to that next level.
[whimpering and muttering]
- You can totally
cut this tension
with a knife right now.
- [crying]
I'm so sick of this.
♪ ♪
I think it messes
with every single one of us.
- Why does she always win?
[sniffs]
It's just not fair.
- And tonight,
the drama continues.
[birds chirping]
[water trickling]
- [sniffling]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- I don't--I--
[whimpers]
- At the group date
last night,
there was drama
with everything that happened
at the last cocktail party
with Kelsey and Hannah.
I don't think it's resolved.
- I just would never
do that to someone.
Why would I steal champagne
and, like--that makes no sense.
- Then--then talk to her
about that.
- Two of you [indistinct]
it forward,
and if she wants to say
that I'm a liar,
that I'm a champagne stealer--
'cause I would not
steal champagne.
- I guess Hannah Ann
had said that
she was getting bullied
by Kelsey.
I wouldn't go to Peter.
- Yeah.
- Like, I would confront her
about it.
- Yeah, exactly.
- And she needs to do it
before the next Rose Ceremony.
- Right, 'cause, like,
you just never know
when someone's
gonna, like, snap,
crackle, or [bleep] pop.
With those two, you just don't
know what's gonna happen.
- We knew there
was gonna be something,
because the night before
was whenever everything--
like, you know,
[bleep] hit the fan.
It was just kind of like,
"Here we go."
- The whole champagne thing
was just bound to explode.
I'm sure Peter's exhausted
from dealing with this thing
for two days.
So, like, who knows
how today's date might go.
♪ ♪
[light music]
- Last night
and getting the date card,
I was so excited
about going on a date today.
But I'm really nervous
and anxious.
A fear of mine is that,
after everything that's gone on
the last few days,
is he in a place
where he's able
to be vulnerable
with me today?
- Have the best date ever.
[indistinct chatter]
- Hey, hey, hey.
- Hi.
- Look how cute!
- Aww.
Hello.
- I love this flannel.
- Should we, uh,
head out of here?
- Bye, guys.
I can't wait to leave
all of everything
that's going on here behind
and focus in
on our relationship.
[upbeat music]
This is so much fun.
- I am so looking forward
to today...
- Me too.
- And spending it with you.
'Cause yesterday
was a little--just weird.
- No, I--I was--
I was worried about you.
Like, there's a lot
of, like, tension and conflict.
I'm here to focus
on our relationship,
and I don't like all that.
- No, I could tell...
- So I'm happy to--
- Very early on.
- To have this time with you,
because, like,
in that environment--
- No distractions.
- Yeah.
- From the beginning,
Victoria P.'s
kind of showed me that
nurturing side that she has.
It's the reason, you know,
I'm asking her
on a one-on-one.
So this is my hometown
right now.
What I actually--
If you make a left here,
that's where my house is.
- Really?
- I'm excited to give her
a taste of my hometown.
This is my favorite
wine bar.
- Oh, awesome.
- It's a really fun,
chill vibe.
- Red wine or white wine?
- I'm a red wine kind of guy.
- Yes!
Yes! He passed the test.
- Yeah? Yes.
I have a fun day planned.
Something I love to do
with my friends,
big part of my life,
and I have a little surprise
waiting for her.
But we gotta look the part
if we're gonna do this.
[upbeat country music]
Oh, yeah.
- Yes. I like it.
- So what do you think?
Is this your style?
- Yeah.
We can be, like...
- Are you up for this?
- Cowgirl and cowboy today.
- Yeah. Look at these boots.
- Oh, yeah.
- Wow.
Are these roses?
- Oh, my God.
- I mean, roses
look really good with you,
so...
- Oh, you think so?
- I do.
- Okay.
Well, I will...
accept all the roses,
those on the boots included.
- That's what
I wanted to hear.
- It feels so good
just to soak in
every single moment
that I have with just him.
These are good.
- We doing some Irish dancing?
What's this about?
- [laughs]
I get to just be goofy
and just be who I am
with someone
that I really, really like.
- So, my friends and I,
we love to line dance.
Um, I want to teach you
a line dance.
All right? Ready?
- I'll just try. Okay.
- And one, two, three, boom.
One, two, three, boom.
Inside, inside, inside,
outside...
- I want nothing more,
at this point,
than for Peter and I
to fall in love.
This is--I like this.
- We just go in a circle
like this
and hold each other
nice and close.
- Mm-hmm.
Peter is an incredible
fricking man,
and I never thought
that could be the kind of man
that I was worthy of having.
And it feels really good.
[giggles]
- Got our hat, our jacket.
- My man.
- I think you're
looking the part.
I got my girl.
Let's get out of here.
I'm having so much fun
with her,
but I still have
one big surprise for her.
This is a place where I go
all the time with my friends.
Remember what I taught you?
- I'm gonna try to remember.
- All right.
We're about to show it off
right now.
- [laughs]
- Let's go.
I'm really excited that I get
to share this with her.
You know,
if this all goes well,
you know, we could be doing
this on the regular.
[country music playing]
♪ ♪
- ♪ I got rules to live by ♪
- Yee-haw!
- ♪ That do me all right ♪
♪ ♪
♪ I lie low,
but I feel fine ♪
- Music's going crazy.
The crowd's just great energy.
It was so fun
seeing her smiling
and just having a good time.
♪ ♪
Victoria's looking gorgeous
on the dance floor.
She's impressed me
like no other today.
♪ ♪
[crowd cheering]
- Dancing with Peter,
I feel like the luckiest
stinkin' girl in the world
that I get to share
these moments with him
after the last few days
that he's had.
This man is really incredible
and also...pretty sexy.
[harmonica playing]
- Impressed me
with those moves.
- I've got some moves
I didn't know I had.
I've definitely got more
than just a crush
on Peter right now,
and it feels really,
really good.
- [laughs]
- That was so much fun.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- Did you like that?
- Yeah, I did.
- It's like--thank you.
- I was pretty nervous.
- Thank you.
- This morning, I got up,
and I didn't hear a whole lot
about what happened yesterday,
but I was concerned for you,
and I know that you've
got a lot on your plate,
and you're trying
to, you know, figure out
who the person
is for you in this,
and all I know is, for certain,
is how I feel about you.
I definitely didn't expect
to be so comfortable
and to feel the way that I--
I do right now.
- 100%.
- I'm a little--
I'm a little smitten
right now, I think.
- [laughing]
I'm a little smitten too.
But I'm okay with that.
- Yeah.
- That's what I'm looking for.
Today has been so much fun.
I love seeing you out there.
- [laughs]
- You are the cutest.
You got moves.
You make me really,
really excited.
♪ ♪
[singing continues,
crowd cheering]
This was my kind of day today.
I had so much fun
with Victoria.
- ♪ We've been talking
since the show was over ♪
♪ And I know it's all mine ♪
This is why I'm so excited
to have this opportunity,
for this kind of feeling
right now that I'm feeling.
- ♪ He said, "Son,
can I give you some advice? ♪
♪ 'Cause I can see that...♪
- It just feels
so comfortable and natural.
Being able to continue
to see her heart
and how beautiful it is
just makes me really happy.
- ♪ So don't you ever ♪
♪ Bring young girls home ♪
[crowd cheering]
- The chemistry's there
like crazy.
I could've just found
my dancing partner for life.
- ♪ Just love one woman ♪
♪ And play the hell
out of a guitar ♪
[cheers and applause]
- She called me
some pretty filthy things.
- You can both
move forward from this,
but you have to sit down,
you have to hash it out.
[dramatic music]
Just so you know,
she's walking this way, okay?
- Okay.
- Yeah?
- Hey.
- Thank you.
- Do you guys wanna talk?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I'll just leave.
- I do have real feelings
for Peter.
I would be upset
if I got sent home
because of the conversation
that they had.
Being called a bully
isn't okay,
and this whole thing has just
been taken way too far,
and I'm hoping that it--
it stops here.
♪ ♪
So...
last night wasn't nice.
- Mm-hmm.
- You have to understand,
the word "bully," that's a very
serious accusation to make,
and I'm not okay with that,
and I will not tolerate it.
- After the "finasco"
of the champagne-stealing
incident,
you were calling me a bitch.
You were saying
that I was fake.
You were saying--something
about a princess comment.
- Using unkind words to you,
I apologize for that,
but that is not bullying.
It's not.
- Well, we can--
we can agree to disagree
on that.
- How can you act like this?
- Yeah.
I mean, we're all here
for Peter.
We're going into the third
Rose Ceremony, and we are still
talking about a champagne
bottle that got popped.
- I'm not a champagne stealer.
- I never intended--
That was a h--enormous--
- It's not about the champagne.
- Oh, okay.
It's not about the champagne.
- I don't even
really like champagne.
- Why would I want
that negative attention?
- I don't know,
because I don't know you.
- You--you know what?
You don't know me,
so why call me fake?
- And you don't--
- Why don't--
why call me the B word?
- Honey...
- I'm not going around
"Ba-da-da-da-da,"
like,
callin' people B words...
- I'm just tired
of all the drama.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause we never talked about
the champagne before that.
- Hannah.
- Why are we so focused
on this champagne bottle?
Why aren't we more focused
on our connection with him?
- Exactly.
- I would never steal
someone's champagne.
Like, I promise you
on everything,
I would not steal
your champagne,
and it hurts me that
we're both in this position.
You've had plenty of time
to come up and, like,
talk to me about it,
and I know what I said
wasn't nice, but--
- You--you--you told me
to "stay the [bleep]
away from you," so...
- So we're gonna
make this about me now.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- This is so stupid.
I'm never gonna look at
a bottle of champagne the same.
♪ ♪
- Coming up tonight...
- She did ask me to lie,
and like, that's not who I am.
- Hmm...
- This drama is just, like,
taking over the house.
- She puts on the pretty
little princess facade,
and she's manipulating Peter.
She'll get a rude awakening.
[air horn blares]
- Wake up, bitches!
The queen is back.
[laughter, screaming]
- It's beginning
to become very clear
what their true colors are.
- You're such a bitch.
- Somebody is not
being genuine with me.
- [crying]
Everything about me
is being called into question.
[crying]
- There's been a little bit
of a change tonight.
♪ ♪
This is now the final rose.
- I don't want him
to give up on me yet.
I have so much to give
and so much to offer.
♪ ♪
[engine whirring]
[soft music]
- All right.
So what do you think?
- This is frickin' perfect.
- Yeah?
Perfect way to end
this perfect day.
- I could not have dreamt
of a better day
to be surrounded
by the things that you love.
- [chuckles]
Milady.
- Yes.
I'm feeling really good
right now.
I had an amazing day
with Victoria.
My heart's very happy
right now.
I'm thankful for that,
'cause I needed it.
I think I could've found
my dance partner today.
- I think you could've.
- I like what I saw.
You know, we had
a lot of fun today.
Really lighthearted.
But I'm excited
to get a little bit more
serious tonight.
She's just
such a beautiful person,
inside and out,
and I just want to see,
why is she the way she is
and hopefully allow her
to feel comfortable
to open up with me.
Today...
today went so good for me.
I knew it was gonna
be good with you
from the first night
to this first
one-on-one with you.
You have just allowed
your heart to come through,
and you just have
that nurturing side
and...so much love to give.
And I see that.
- Like, I am a caregiver,
and you know,
but I'm, like,
such a positive person,
but like, there are,
I think...
You know, like, reasons
why I am that way.
Like...
[sniffs]
'Cause, like, saying this
is difficult, you know?
You know, my--
my dad passed away
when I was really young,
and after that,
my mom really,
um, had a hard time
and...kind of fell
into addiction.
And, um...
[whispers]
Like...
- [whispering]
I'm sorry to hear that.
- [quietly whimpering]
And, um...
I grew up, like,
in and out of, like--
we grew up in and out
of shelters growing up.
Um...
[sniffs]
My mom, like, really
struggled, and...
Like, I really had
to be the rock for her
and for my sister.
You know, like,
we didn't know, like--
I didn't know, like,
if my sister and I
would even have food.
Like, have anything to eat,
and I would literally, like,
like, peel a potato
and, like, cut it in half
and just, like,
put salt and pepper on it,
and that would be, like--
I'd make sure, like, my sister
was, like, taken care of.
[inhales deeply]
And...
[sniffles]
I dreamed a lot of dreams,
and one of my dreams
was just, like,
to get out of that place
and--and to have--
to have, like,
a happy and healthy life
and to make something of myself
and to have a family.
I think it's affected
my relationships sometimes,
because I didn't...
feel deserving of someone...
[whispers]
Like you.
[sniffling]
[whispers]
Sorry, Peter.
- It's all right.
- [whispers]
I'm sorry.
- Don't apologize.
- I just feel so grateful,
because I feel like you've
shown me the kind of love
that I deserve.
- [chuckles softly]
You deserve it all.
- [sniffs]
I was so scared
to have this conversation,
because I know it's a lot,
and I know it's, like, heavy,
and you've had a heavy week.
- No. No. This--
- I just, like, have--
- This is what matters.
You are what matters
to me, okay?
Thank you for--
for opening up to me and--
and telling me that.
I can't even imagine
what that must've been like
growing up.
It just shows me
what kind of person you are.
- I just want you
to know who I am
and, like, about my life.
I just didn't always
feel worthy of this.
- You are.
Are you kidding me?
- And I feel so good
right now.
I don't know if this
is like the stars aligning
or what this is.
- [laughs quietly]
I...
Who knows if the stars
are aligned for us?
Um...
a couple days
before all this started,
I just--I had
a really special moment
where I felt like
I just knew
this was gonna work.
I just started, like,
talking to God,
and I just was like,
"I don't know where she is,
but watch over her."
And the second
that I said that,
a shooting star
went across the sky.
And she could be here
right now, sitting next to me.
- Yeah, she could be.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
I have never been
inspired by someone
so much in my entire life,
and I mean that
from the bottom of my heart.
You have shown me
so much tonight
and shown me
so much of your heart.
- [giggles]
♪ ♪
- It feels so right...
with you.
Like, insanely right.
And it's so early on,
I know,
but...
that's totally okay with me.
Victoria,
will you accept this rose?
- Yes.
I will gladly accept this rose.
- Come here.
♪ ♪
- This was one
of the best days
of my entire life.
Tonight, Peter accepted me
for who I am
and saw my heart,
and I couldn't have asked
for anything more.
After today, I feel
like I could see
the life that I always
dreamt to have.
- If we could take
one airplane...
- Mm-hmm?
- Which one are we taking?
- This is my favorite.
- Yeah?
- This is my very favorite.
I am falling in love
with Peter.
The more that I can
just see his heart,
the more that I believe
that this is a life
that I'm worthy of.
- [laughs]
He could be my knight
in shining armor
and that he could be the person
that I'm meant to spend
forever with.
This is a dream come true.
- [chuckles]
This is.
- I'm just so happy.
- This hat's from y'all's date,
and I'm stealing it,
and it's mine now.
- It's mine!
- I'm ready to, like,
control this party.
Let's go.
I'm testing out
that pilot wife life, dude.
Like, you come home,
I got my red wine,
got my captain's hat.
Like...
"Welcome home, Peter."
Basically, everybody,
like, sees me and thinks--
because of pageants
and what I do--
that I'm, like, the sweet,
little, elegant, proper thing
and, "Ugh, no, don't touch me,
Don't look at me."
- You got a wild side to you?
- [bleep], yeah, dude.
Bro, I get nasty.
- Oh, okay.
- No, I'm like, very good
at putting on face
when I need to.
I mean, if Peter wants
to be in the Mile High Club,
I will gladly join in.
[knock on door]
- Oh, my God.
- It scares me every time.
- Cheers to dates.
- Cheers, all of you bitches!
I love you!
- All I go off of
is what I see in people.
With Alayah, I could tell
something is off
about that girl.
Just her actions
since we've been here
kind of just, you know,
makes you go sideways
a little bit.
- Group date, group date,
group date.
- Shh, shh, shh.
- She is not the type of girl
I surround myself with.
She's the type of girl
that I've always avoided.
I just don't want
to be around her.
- Kiarra...
- Yay!
- Sarah...
- [clicks tongue]
- Tammy.
- Eee! Yay!
- [laughs]
- Kelley.
- Yay!
- Yeah!
Shiann.
- Oh...
- Savannah.
- Hallelujah!
- Sydney.
- Mm!
- Yay!
[suspenseful music]
- Alayah.
- Oh, man.
- [inhales, sighs]
- Okay.
- It says, "I love surprises.
I hope you do too."
- Surprise.
- Yes.
- I don't like surprises.
- [scoffs]
- Well, wait, wait, wait.
So I really want to know.
Baby girl, how do you feel
not getting a date?
- Um...
- You're such a bitch.
You're like, "Oh, I'm going."
- [laughs]
- He is so deserving
of someone that is 100%
here for him.
She is just all fake,
and I hope that Peter
will be able to, like,
weed that out.
- So many feelings!
I hate surprises.
♪ ♪
[crickets chirping]
[rooster crowing]
[light snoring]
[soft whistling]
[mischievous music]
[gate creaking]
♪ ♪
[insect buzzing]
- I'm back, bitches!
[militaristic music]
I helped Hannah
on "The Bachelorette,"
and now I'm here
to help Peter,
and I just hope
that I can show him
who these ladies really are.
So I brought in my henchwomen,
and they're about to rock
these girls' world.
[whistle blasts]
♪ ♪
- Rise and shine, ladies!
- Let's get up!
Let's get up! Let's get up!
♪ ♪
- Ladies, the queen is back!
- Up, up, up!
Rise and shine, ladies!
- I'm like, "Who is this?"
Who the [bleep]
is yelling at me?
- Get up, get up, get up!
- Okay, okay!
- Wake up, you maggot!
Rise and shine!
[alarm blaring]
- Next thing I know,
I just see feathers everywhere,
and I was so confu--
- Wake up, bitches.
It is date day.
Meet me downstairs.
Let's go.
- What the heck is happening?
[alarm blaring]
Demi walks in here,
the queen,
and I'm just like,
"What is happening?"
Like, it was just, like--
it was a lot to take in.
♪ ♪
- All right, ladies.
Y'all look haggard [bleep].
[laughter]
But Peter's one
of my good friends,
I love him, so I asked him
if I could plan a date,
and he said yes,
so I brought some backup.
I've got Cham-pain
over here
and Killer.
Rrr.
[laughter]
So they're gonna grab you guys
some outfits.
- [gasps]
Oh!
- These outfits
are for the girls
that are on today's dates,
and you have to get dressed
quickly,
because Peter's
going to be here in an hour
to pick you guys up.
- All right.
- Okay.
- See you later.
[excited chatter]
- Tammy.
- Kelley.
- We got these bags
with our names on 'em...
- Oh, yes.
- Wow.
- Oh, okay.
- Oh! Oh!
- And inside of it
was, like,
a cute pajama "linger-y" set.
- ♪ Hey! ♪
- Y'all, I have
straight-up lingerie.
[women exclaiming]
- Come on. Come on.
- Y'all...
- Wait. What?
- Y'all, am I in a muumuu?
- Ahh!
- Am I in a muumuu?
[women shouting]
- Savannah!
[laughter]
- I am wearing a muumuu today!
I get the muumuu.
What the [bleep]?
How is he gonna take me
seriously in a muumuu?
[upbeat music]
- Where are your pajamas?
- I didn't get the memo.
[laughs]
Is this actually
how you sleep?
all: No!
- Demi brought these for us.
- Oh!
- You really think that--
- Do you legitimately--
[laughter, chatter]
- I have eight
wonderful ladies
going on the date today,
and I have absolutely no idea
what I'm doing.
The date's completely
in Demi's hands.
All right. You ready for this?
- Yeah. Sure.
- But hopefully it's a surprise
that I like too.
♪ ♪
[cheers and applause]
- Let's go. Let's do it.
Whoo!
- Let's go, let's go!
- We get there,
hot girls in lingerie,
and we are at
a freaking saloon,
which makes me really wonder
what we are doing.
[cheers and applause]
[rock music]
♪ ♪
- We come in,
and you have Cham-pain
and Killer
just going at it in the ring.
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Finish her!
[cheers and applause]
Demi.
- Hi, Peter.
- Hey, Demi.
- All right, so I know
that there's a lot of tension
in the mansion,
so I wanted to give you ladies
the opportunity
to let out that aggression
in Demi's
Extreme Pillow Fight Club.
[cheers and applause]
Yeah!
- Smackdown.
- But remember,
we are here to fight
for Peter's heart,
so I would advise
you guys today
to really let go and have fun.
And I think it's gonna
be pretty hot to watch too.
[laughter]
- I'm excited for this.
Let's go.
- Yeah.
All right, ladies!
Yeah!
[upbeat music]
- One! Two!
- Whoo!
- There has been a lot
of drama,
so I think today
we're gonna be able to
let out some of this
pent-up tension.
But we're gonna keep it fun,
keep it lighthearted,
because, you know,
I'm fighting for Peter's love.
- This is my kind of game,
let me tell you.
I was on the varsity wrestling
team in high school, so...
I'ma whack somebody.
[cheers and applause]
- Hello, everybody.
Welcome to Demi's Extreme
Pillow Fight Club.
I'm your host,
Chris Harrison.
Joining me once again,
Hollywood icon
and pillow-fighting legend
Fred Willard.
[cheers and applause]
- I have an interesting fact.
- What is that?
- "Pillow fight"
comes from the Greek word
"pilloweth smacketh
in the face-eth."
[rock music]
- I think you just
made that up, Fred.
- I did--
I just made that up.
- So in one corner, we have...
Tammy "The Taminator"!
[cheers and applause]
[crowd chanting]
Tammy! Tammy! Tammy!
- And in the other corner,
we have...
Kelley "The Prose-cutie"!
[cheers and applause]
- Go prosecute her!
- I'm a little nervous.
I mean, who wants
to see their attorney
dressed in lingerie
on a TV show?
- Are you ready to slumber?
[all whooping]
[bell dings]
- Oh!
♪ ♪
- Fred, we have had
a pillow explosion.
♪ ♪
- Oh! Oh!
- Tammy is like a little
Tasmanian devil.
She's tackling this girl
left and right.
- Uh-oh, she's going down
again.
Oh, no!
- Is that legal?
- No, Fred, and Tammy
has been disqualified.
- Ahh!
Huh-huh-huh-huh!
[bell dings]
[cheers and applause]
Shiann "The Shianimal"
is really taking it
to the muumuu.
♪ ♪
Savannah's down.
Oh! Savannah's down.
[bell dinging]
[blade swishes]
- Good job.
You killed it.
- Thank you.
- Alayah, bring it, baby!
- Having a history
in pageants,
I think Alayah's
gonna be worried
too much about messing
her hair up.
[bell dings]
[cheers and applause]
♪ ♪
- Let's go!
- Everybody has this idea
that I'm this prim and proper
pageant girl,
but I wanna fight for Peter,
and I wanna, like,
fight for my time
and fight for his heart.
♪ ♪
- Whoo!
Oh! Oh!
Like, I was--
I was feeling that.
[cheers and applause]
- Whoa!
♪ ♪
- Fred, it looks like Sarah
"The Sleepwalker"
is being sent back to bed.
[cheers and applause]
[crowd groans]
[whistle blasts]
- You know, Chris,
this reminds me
of a photo you showed me
of your bedroom
after New Year's Eve
last year.
- That was between
you and I, Fred.
- Right, right...
- It is time
for the championship round.
[cheers and applause]
- Who's it gonna be?
- I pick the two people
who I saw the most effort from.
Alayah
"The Royal Pain."
[cheers and applause]
- Peter's about to see
a new side to me.
He doesn't know
that I can get down and dirty.
- And...
"Syd Vicious."
- "Syd Vicious"!
- Let's go, let's go!
- Time with Peter is precious,
so I mean, I don't really care
about dirty play.
I go in there, I see red,
and I [bleep] go.
[bell dinging]
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic music]
- Whoo!
♪ ♪
- Uh-oh. Hair pulling, Fred.
Hair pulling.
♪ ♪
- Show me you want it!
[cheers and applause]
- I was trying
to fight for Peter,
and I was just, like,
pounding, pounding, pounding.
- Put her down!
[audience groaning]
[bell dinging]
- And then she decides
to sit on me.
What am I supposed to do?
[bleep] elephant
sitting on a rat,
how you gonna get up?
- Alayah!
[cheers and applause]
- I am the champion!
- Your prize right here.
[cheers and applause]
- I won the crown.
I won a kiss from Peter.
I am just on top of the world.
- You are the queen
of the bedroom, for sure.
So...
[cheers and applause]
- Nobody likes to lose,
but she puts on the pretty
little princess facade
and the pageant queen,
and she wins everything.
Maybe that might be true,
but she'll get
a rude awakening
sooner rather than later.
- Shall we get out of here?
- Yeah.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- Alayah is manipulative.
She's fake.
She thinks
that this is a game.
You sound so rehearsed
and, like,
so "on."
- That she asked that I not
tell producers
that we knew one another.
- With Alayah,
yes, there are flags...
- I'm not lying to you
about anything.
- But what I think I see
is the truth.
- She's manipulating Peter.
Like, 1,000%.
- Future Alayah Weber,
out.
[soft guitar music]
♪ ♪
- Oh, my gosh.
- This is amazing.
Wow.
- This is so cute.
- I love all of this.
I've had a good day today.
I won the pillow-fighting
competition today,
and this is my prize.
- Where are we going?
- When Sydney and I wrestled
today and duked it out,
the claws definitely came out
a little bit,
but Sydney saw red
and was, like, going at it,
so I don't really know
what's going on there.
- I just think it's cool
to kind of do things sometimes
that brings you back
to your childhood,
so I'm happy that you all
embraced it.
- He's seen the sweet Alayah,
and he's now seen kind of
a little bit more
fire and fight in me,
so knowing how valuable
that time is with him,
I am determined
to make the most of it.
♪ ♪
Do you mind if I kidnap you?
- But of course.
- Please.
- All right.
- Come on over this way.
[tense music]
- Today, me and Alayah
went at it,
and I think
I was the clear winner,
but just--people like Alayah
just win in this world,
and she keeps winning.
- You look really good
with a crown on.
- I've had plenty of crowns
in my life.
- Alayah is the type of girl
that puts on the pretty
little princess facade
and flaunts herself
in front of the cameras
in a absolute
orchestrated show.
Just frustrates me because
if, like--if you're
coming in here
and putting on a façade,
then you're
cheating Peter out of
really getting everything
out of this that he can.
- Pretty aggressive there
on the, uh--
on the mattress.
- Look!
Can you see, like--
- Oh, my God.
This is from the fight?
- Yes.
- It was a catfight.
- It was intense.
- Legit. Wow.
- That was frickin' hard.
But I wanted to show you
that I was gonna fight for you,
so there you go.
- And you did.
That you did.
I was very impressed.
- But I mean, it worked out,
'cause now I feel like
you have seen, like,
the sweet side of me
and the innocent side
and all those sides,
and today was the fighter
and the strong side.
But you know, I've kind of been
wanting to be a little bit
more vulnerable with you
and, like, open up
a little bit more,
just about--like, I've been
through some stuff in my life.
I've been abandoned a lot
by friends or relationships
or people that
I've cared a lot about.
So this experience
is tricky for me,
'cause I do worry about that--
going days without seeing you
and wondering,
like, is he forgetting about me
while he's gone?
- I can promise you
I'm not forgetting about you.
- I worry about it, though.
- I promise you
I'm not, though.
I will say I do have a really
good feeling about you,
and I'm not just saying that.
I...
there's just something
about you that
just really,
really draws me in,
and...yeah.
You just get me really excited.
- One of my girlfriends
is a pilot wife,
and so she gave me
a little advice...
- Oh, okay.
- Coming into this.
- What do you think
about dating a pilot?
- Oh, I love it.
- Yeah?
- I wouldn't be here
if I wasn't about
that pilot wife life.
- [chuckles]
That's true. Yeah.
- You should've seen me
yesterday.
I was wearing
the--the captain's hat.
I was walking around with it,
and they were like,
"Alayah, what are you doing?"
I'm like, "I'm testing out
that pilot wife life."
You know, just hanging out.
- [laughing]
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
- You like it a little bit?
- I love it.
- Yeah?
- Yeah, I'm here for it.
- Look at this.
- Oh, that's my crown.
- Uh-huh.
- No.
♪ ♪
- Wow.
- What you think?
- Absolutely gorgeous.
Alayah has a very positive,
fun energy about her
that I totally connect with.
She really opened up
and just really impressed me.
I have so much hope for this.
I'm just--I'm really,
really excited for the future.
♪ ♪
- How was your time with him?
- It was really good.
- Good.
- You know, I really wanted to,
I guess, open up to him
and be more vulnerable
and more, like, you know,
explain to him why I'm here.
And he was, of course,
amazing and receptive,
and it was just really good.
It made me feel super good.
- Alayah is manipulative,
she's fake,
because she thinks
that this is a game.
He deserves someone
that's up-front, honest,
and like, really, really,
really open with him,
and I just feel like
that's not her.
- I didn't hurt you today,
did I?
Everybody was like,
"Did she pull your hair?
Did she pull it?"
And I'm like, "Did she?"
- Do you, like, work at all?
- Tsss. I have three jobs.
"Do you work?"
- I didn't know.
I never asked you.
- Yeah.
- 'Cause some girls say, like,
their job
is being Miss whatever.
I don't know if that--
- Oh.
Yeah. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I feel that.
Like, Miss USA,
you have to quit your job.
Like, you can't have a job.
- Do you feel like
you, like,
keep a lot of that in you
to this day,
like pageantry and like
the training and stuff?
- Yeah, yeah, people kinda
keep calling me on it--
You know, "You're always
so prim and proper
and perfect and like..."
And I'm just like,
"I'm so used to it."
Like, that's just kind of been
my life for eight years.
- Yeah.
- And I've always
been a titleholder.
Like, I've held several titles,
and so I'm so used
to being that.
- Knowing what to say,
the right thing to say,
the right way to look.
- And knowing how not to offend
anybody when I'm saying things
and like, you know, if I don't
want to answer a question,
how to answer
without answering.
Like, those things
are easy for me.
- Yeah.
Like, opening up
and like, being your true core
is kind of hard.
[tense music]
You sound so rehearsed
and like, so--so, like,
"on," you know what I mean?
And if cameras--
you're just, like, "on."
But if you come in here
worrying about how
you're perceived,
then you're not gonna
be your real self to Peter,
and, like, that's
what he's here to find
is, like, a real person.
♪ ♪
But who knows what he wants?
He--he's here to figure it out.
- I don't know.
♪ ♪
- She knows what she's doing,
and she's manipulating Peter.
Like, 1,000%.
She recognizes that
I see through her.
It's not "The Alayah Show."
Like, this is about Peter.
Like, it's just time
to cut the [bleep].
♪ ♪
- How are you?
- Definitely good.
How are you?
- Mm. Good.
I have to be honest with you.
- What's that?
- The beard.
I'm more of the scruff
kind of girl.
- Maybe I should shave it off
a little bit?
- Do the scruff.
- Do the scruff?
- Yeah.
- Take it down?
- A little bit.
- Okay.
I will. Just for you.
- [laughing]
- All right?
[chuckles]
I don't know what it is
about Kelley.
I like her a lot.
There's something about her
that just intrigues me
and that just keeps me, um,
kind of wanting more.
- Tell me your thoughts.
- Um...
- What's on Peter's mind?
- Uh, you are...
When I say this is already
starting to work for me,
you are a big reason
why I feel that way already.
- Good.
- And...
Are you doing good, though?
Like, you think this is...
- Yeah.
- Like, something that you
could actually...
Like, be real with me
when I ask you that.
You think this is something
that could work for you?
- Do I necessarily fit in
to, like, this process
and like, how all this works?
Absolutely not.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I'm so out
of my comfort zone.
Like, I honestly think
I would've gone home by now
if it wasn't worth it.
[chuckles]
[soft music]
- She's an attorney.
She's very, very smart.
And a lot of the qualities
I'm looking for
that I'm really attracted to,
she has.
Today was perfect.
Tonight's perfect.
This is off to a great start.
You're so much fun.
I love your energy.
- I was, like, literally
so worried about it.
I'm like,
"He just thinks I'm a bro."
- Are you kidding me?
I don't do this
to my bros, so...
♪ ♪
This is working.
This is moving
in the right direction.
I can really see the girls
that I'm spending time with
as a potential wife.
- How you been?
- I've been good.
- Yeah.
- It's been a--
it's been a fun day.
- Yeah.
- How was it for you?
- It's been hard this week.
- Has it?
- Mm-hmm, it really has.
Sometimes I get in my head
about, like,
like, am I someone
that you would want to be with?
Like, really?
- Do you not think that
right now?
- I mean...
- Like, be completely honest
with me.
- Who you do, like,
have stronger
connections with right now,
it seems like
I'm just, like,
the polar opposite
of those people.
- Listen.
I really like what I see
so far with you.
I don't know.
Your heart just shined
through to me immediately,
and you've already
kind of opened
yourself up to me
and let me see who you are.
Why do you think
you're so different?
- Um, just like--
just the imagery of this
makes girls...
like, not be themselves
or, um, like,
put on, like, a facade
that you might really,
really like in the beginning,
and then, like,
when you're in real life,
like, realize that
it's not real, you know?
- Mm-hmm.
So you definitely,
though, do see
some of these girls
maybe aren't being
very genuine with me?
[tense music]
- When I'm in the house
with some girls,
it's two different things,
and like,
when the cameras show up
and the lights are on
and there's that time
for some camera time,
like, it's a whole
different person.
And like, it's just so...
like, it's just so artificial.
And I just, like, don't want
you to get blinded by that.
♪ ♪
- Like, that's
such a fear of mine,
that I could fall for someone
and they're...
you know...they're fake.
I mean, I saw it with Hannah,
like, last season,
seeing her fall for someone
that, you know, wasn't there
for the right reasons.
You know, I don't--
I just do not want fake.
- Like, I love y'all,
but I don't wanna know
y'all's relationship with him,
because I just wanna focus
on my relationship with him.
Like...
Hey, you.
- Hi.
- Hey, hey.
Hoo...right?
It's a little chilly out.
- Want some blankets?
- Thanks.
Um, there is--
there's something
that's kind of stuck in my mind
that I can't,
uh, move on from yet,
and um...
There were some concerns
in regards
to just some people here
possibly not being real
with me,
and...
I saw kind of firsthand
what happened last season.
And my biggest fear in this
is possibly getting blindsided,
and I just--I hate feeling
like I might possibly be
being fooled right now.
[dramatic music]
Sydney, um...
♪ ♪
Sorry to kind of put you
on the spot,
um, but you had mentioned
that there were people
that, um,
maybe are different off-camera
or different in the house
when I'm not there
and then when they are with me,
and I trust you,
and I want to just
kind of squash this now.
♪ ♪
- Um...
maybe Alayah.
Like, maybe you put on
a little bit
for the--just for the imagery
of things.
♪ ♪
- I mean, does anybody else
feel that way?
I mean, we're all
living together at this point,
so I feel like everybody's
kind of gotten to see me,
day in, day out.
♪ ♪
- Listen, I just ask,
be real, be raw.
Just be yourself.
I am giving this my everything,
and I'm just, please,
asking you.
If you're not feeling it,
if you're doing this
for the cameras,
for any other reason
besides seeing if this
can work with me,
I do not have time for that.
♪ ♪
- Well, I was having
a really good day.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
I guess I just don't understand
why you felt the need
to say anything.
- Just because of our
conversation earlier.
- So you feel like
I'm being fake.
You feel like I'm putting up
a front 'cause there's cameras.
- I feel like
you give reactions.
Your reactions
are a little bit--
Alayah, come on.
There's a little bit dramatic.
- I'm not denying.
But that's still--
- Okay, if you're not denying,
then we see eye to eye then.
- Okay, so now this whole
night, for me,
has been ruined,
'cause we had this
great conversation,
and I, like, opened--
- I didn't ruin your night.
- But what I'm saying
is tonight--
- Maybe I brought it to light
and you didn't want me
to do that.
When the cameras are on,
you do react a little too much,
and it looks
a little bit fabricated.
- But you don't know me
outside of this.
Like, this is--
that's my personal--
I have a big personality.
- So at home you just, like,
fall out on the floor and--
- Yeah.
- Maybe that's what it is.
- It just sucks that now
you made Peter doubt me.
- I didn't make Peter
do anything,
but I will never lie,
and I will always
stand by my word,
and I did that.
- I believe you.
- Okay, well, good, so don't
ever say I constructed this,
'cause I didn't.
- I'm not saying that.
- And that's not cool.
- But at the end of the day,
you chose to say my name,
and now he's
walking away and doubting.
- I chose to say your name
because what do you want me
to say, Tammy's name?
I don't feel that
about Tammy.
So what do you want me to say?
♪ ♪
Stupid, stupid, stupid.
- Hey, Peter?
Can I chat with you?
- Mm-hmm.
- I don't even know
what the hell just happened,
and I guess I would love
to get your...
your idea of what--
what just happened,
'cause I am very confused.
- [sighs] Uh...I mean,
I'm pretty confused too.
Um...
Like, that freaks me out
so much
that I possibly could end up
developing feelings for someone
that is not being genuine
with me.
- Yeah, no.
No, I mean, I get that.
I completely get that,
and I guess I'm just blindsided
'cause, like, I don't know
what she's talking about.
It just sucks that, like,
I get called into question
about--about
what I'm doing here.
[crying]
- Oh, my God.
- I wouldn't be here if I
didn't feel something for you.
But I do, and it terrifies
the hell out of me.
Like, I was already facing
all these insecurities,
and now to think that, like,
it's possible that you think
that I'm being fake
just sucks.
♪ ♪
- [groans]
I just feel really confused,
I guess, still.
I believe Sydney
when she brought up
those concerns,
but Alayah came over
and talked with me,
and like, I...
believe what she
was telling me.
And I--and I like her a lot.
♪ ♪
- Did I miss anything fun?
- You know, I did respect
Sydney a lot.
She spoke it like she saw it.
I'm looking for that honesty
and for someone that's
not afraid to put me first.
I don't know, I think I'm
just, like, really scared
that I'll start to fall
for someone
that, in the end,
could blindside me
and essentially waste
this entire journey.
I just hope that I'm not
getting fooled.
♪ ♪
So I know tonight, um,
well, it didn't exactly go
how I had hoped, I guess.
I care about navigating
this journey
the best way I know how
to see if this will work for me
in the end.
And Sydney, I appreciate you
being honest with me
and essentially putting me
before everyone else.
That really does mean a lot,
and it shows me a lot.
So, Sydney, will you accept
this rose?
- Thanks.
- I know it's a late night,
and I'm sure you're all
as exhausted as I am.
So I will see you guys,
uh, later.
All right.
All right. Night, guys.
- I know he has feelings
for me,
and I have feelings for him,
and if Sydney just would have
kept her opinions to herself,
like, I would have
been thriving.
I'm not gonna allow him
to dislike me
because of some other person's
opinion,
because at the end of the day,
it's gonna be me and Peter.
♪ ♪
- Coming up...
- She did ask me to lie,
and like, that's not who I am.
- Mm.
- I just feel like
you're not getting, like,
a genuine version.
You're getting, like,
the version
that is the most perfect.
- But you need to figure
that out for yourself.
- This drama is just, like,
taking over the house.
- I was fooled,
and I have to guard my heart.
- There's been a little bit
of a change tonight.
This is now the final rose.
♪ ♪
[soft music]
- I just feel like
I was just so blindsided.
Like, completely blindsided.
I don't know where
that came from, like...
And, like, it's somebody
that I don't even have
a relationship with here.
Like, I haven't spent
hardly any time with her.
So it's like...
like she's speaking to my--
like who I am
and my authenticity
when she doesn't know.
- Yeah.
- She doesn't know me at all.
And for her to, like,
turn around and twist it
and make it sound like
I was--like I'm being fake.
This was just such a shock,
and I was so blindsided
by this.
How are we supposed
to keep moving forward
if he has this, like, seed
of doubt in his mind about me?
If Peter decides
to send me home tonight,
I want that to be his
decision, not anybody else's,
and I want to be sure
that I'm able to talk to him
and get all of my thoughts
and feelings across.
Like, I want to ask him
if he trusts me.
[inhales, exhales]
- Good morning.
all: Good morning.
- How's everybody doing?
- Good.
It's good to see everybody.
We all know
it's been a tough week,
and so today
I have some good news.
Peter's gonna come over
and join you
all afternoon
for a pool party.
[cheers and applause]
- I'm pumped.
- Use your time today wisely,
because there will not
be a cocktail party tonight.
We will be going
straight to the Rose Ceremony.
So today is the last time
you will see him
before he makes
a huge decision.
So Peter will be here
in a little bit.
Go have a good time.
All right, ladies.
See you.
- Bye, Chris.
- Thank you.
- I mean, I think, when you
think of pool party,
it's fun, you know.
You got some cocktails
going on,
you're in the pool,
you're hanging out,
very chill vibe.
Gonna be a fun pool party,
hopefully,
if, you know, the drama
doesn't get too crazy.
- There's another
Rose Ceremony tonight,
and there's no cocktail party,
so I think this pool party
is important,
and I think today
will be good for him
to kind of get those questions
that he has answered.
♪ ♪
- Hey, girls.
all: Hi!
- Hello.
Um...
I was looking forward to today,
you know, to have
a fun pool party,
but just being very honest
with all of you,
I'm not really feeling my best.
Um, I unfortunately,
I guess, kind of feel
a little bit of doubt
creeping in with all this.
I am here for one reason--
and I hope you are as well--
to see if we could find magic
at the end of this,
and you know I have
a big decision for tonight
for the Rose Ceremony,
and this is kind of
my opportunity
to get the answers
that I need moving forward.
So that being said,
uh, Sydney, you mind
if I grab you for a second?
- [quietly]
Yeah. Sure.
[tense music]
- How are you?
- Hi.
♪ ♪
How do you feel?
- Just frustrated.
- Yeah, I can tell.
- Really frustrated.
- Yeah.
- Sydney doesn't think
I'm being real,
and I don't want to feel like
I have to prove myself
to Peter,
but unfortunately,
that's kind of just
turned into today's reality.
- [groans]
Well, first,
I just wanted to, uh--
I just--I wanted to apologize
again for last night,
because I--I felt horrible
having to put you
in that position.
- I'm okay.
Um, no, but I do
stand by what I said.
I don't want you
to just take my word
and say, "Okay, if, you know,
Sydney says it,
then it's--it's true."
I want you to do this,
and like,
those are your decisions
and not mine,
so I would just take today
and really, like,
don't look at the outside.
Don't look at all this
and the pretty voice.
Like, really look at them,
and like, if you do that,
I think you'll figure out,
like, what's going on
and, you know.
- Thank you for--
for being so strong
and being someone
that I can lean on.
- We're good.
- Thank you.
- I promise.
Have a good day.
- You too.
[both chuckling]
- I'm not ever
going to apologize
for doing or saying
or being anything.
Sydney felt so comfortable
sharing this opinion
without knowing me at all.
I asked the group collectively.
I've talked to girls
throughout the day,
and nobody has expressed
any concerns to me.
If the girls here are
questioning my authenticity,
that's their own problem.
- I don't think anyone is.
- I don't think so, either,
'cause nobody else
has said that to me.
Nobody's even, like,
hinted at that with me.
- I'm gonna be, like, real.
I love Alayah.
I think she's a great person.
But...
do I think that she, like,
acts a certain way
in front of the camera
when the camera's on?
Yes.
People that have been
in pageants
also know how to turn it on,
but like, you need to figure
that out for yourself.
- Yeah.
- So I have
a big personality.
- Yes.
- Like, I know
that not everybody's
gonna love me in life.
Like, at the end of the day,
I love all of y'all,
but I want Peter.
- And if you love yourself--
- And as long as
he has feelings for me
and he feels confident, like,
me being authentic and real,
that's all I care about.
- Sydney was not wrong
in her speculation of Alayah
in the sense that, you know,
there's a certain,
"Oh, the cameras are here."
You know what I mean?
- She kind of puts it on
for them.
- Yeah.
- Like, I'm never
gonna apologize
for being a pageant girl.
I loved that part of my life.
It's over now,
and I will never apologize,
'cause I am so proud of that--
- There's nothing negative
about it.
- There's nothing
negative about it.
♪ ♪
- I feel like some people
just kind of turn it on
a little bit for the cameras.
Maybe it's just, like,
the background that--
that she has
and like, pageants and like
maybe she's--
it's just more normal for her.
- You're talking about Alayah?
- Yeah.
I mean, I've just never been
drawn to her as a person.
Like, we'll be hanging out,
and then all of a sudden,
the cameras will come on,
and like, her voice goes up,
like, five octaves.
- My girlfriend makes literally
the best spicy margarita--
jalapeño margarita--
[high-pitched]
Hi.
I'm like, mm.
- You do notice that?
- Like, I don't know,
I just feel like
you're not getting, like,
a genuine version.
You're getting, like,
the version
that is the most perfect,
and I don't want you to end up,
at the end of this,
being like, "Oh, that's not
who I thought..."
- Mm-hmm.
- "It was."
- What I don't get is, like,
if she says she has
a problem with somebody,
why don't you go up
to that somebody first,
get your facts, and then
talk to him about it?
- Exactly, like, just because
it's your opinion
doesn't mean it's a fact,
and that's why I'm so pissed.
I would never go talk to Peter
about another relationship,
because his relationship
with that person
is not my relationship
with him.
Hey, Syd.
- Hey. What's up?
- Can I steal you?
Can we just go chat?
- Where do you wanna go?
- Let's go down there.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
- Sydney does not know me,
she does not know my heart,
she does not know who I am,
and I just don't wanna go home
because of what
she thinks she sees
and what she is choosing
to tell Peter.
So this conversation today
is gonna get really real.
I have no idea
exactly what you told Peter.
I just know that
whatever you said to him
made him question
how real I am
and wonder if, like,
what I'm telling him
isn't real and if it's fake.
- Like, if--if you and Peter
end up in the end of this,
it's not gonna be like this.
It's gonna be you guys
are sitting at home chilling.
You know what I mean?
- I know that.
- So it's like I feel like
he should see all those sides.
He shouldn't just see, like,
the princess Alayah.
[dramatic music]
- But you don't know
our conversations.
- I don't. I don't.
- You don't know
what he and I--you don't
know what he's seen,
because you don't--
you weren't there
for our conversation.
He saw so many sides
of me yesterday...
- Okay. Good.
- And he told me
that he felt like
he's seeing all these sides.
- Do you have feelings?
Do you have emotions
other than perfect--
- Of course I do.
I'm human.
- Okay.
You can't be happy
all the time.
- But I choose not to--
I know.
I haven't had anything
to piss me off.
I mean, this--
- Nothing?
Really?
- This has pissed me off.
The fact that now my character
and my authenticity
coming into question
pisses me off.
You don't care
who you hurt in this process.
- Hurting?
I'm not hurting you.
- You hurt me!
- How did I hurt you?
- My whole, like--my whole
relationship with him
is now in question in his mind,
and he's having doubts.
You don't think that
that had to do with
your conversation with him
last night?
- I don't think--that's not
out of malicious intent.
It's just who I am.
I felt like if I wasn't
up-front and honest,
I would be doing him
a disservice.
- Your opinion of me
is so far from the actual
reality of who I am.
It's one thing if, like, five
girls are walking up to him
and like, "No, like, yeah."
- Alayah, because they don't
have the balls to,
and I do.
- I just wish
that you would just,
like, be honest with him
and tell him--
- Um, Alayah.
Alayah, that was a bad
choice of words, honey,
'cause I've been honest
with him from day one.
- Sydney doesn't have to think
I'm being real,
because at the end of the day,
I know I am.
Her story is not flawless,
because it's an opinion,
and an opinion is not facts.
And I need to clear this up
with Peter.
I know he has feelings for me,
so I'm done crying about it.
I'm done, like, being weak.
I'm not gonna put out my light
just because somebody else
is lying.
♪ ♪
- I, like, genuinely, though,
want you to figure
this thing out.
I, like, hated seeing you sad.
- Yeah. I know.
Mama drama dust.
A lot of today has been
about Alayah and that drama,
and then just being able
to sit down with Madison,
it just makes me forget
about all this.
She's such a genuine person,
and I'm still
just kind of beaming
from that one-on-one date
we had.
Have you been
replaying that night
over and over and over again?
'Cause I have.
That was so cool.
- [gasps]
- And then just that surprise
with the music,
and then my family--
I was like, "Wow."
I'll never forget that night.
- It was the best.
I know. I like...
I felt like it was, like,
so special to me
because family
means so much to you,
but like, family means
so much to me too.
- Mm-hmm.
- And so it was like
a little taste of home.
- Yeah.
- Yeah, and just--
I don't know,
getting to see,
like, a side of you
that, like, nobody else here
has gotten to see.
- That's true.
We shared a very special day.
[soft music]
I needed this so bad.
- Yeah?
- Just to, like, feel good
and get my mind
off of everything.
♪ ♪
Know that I feel
very confident about you.
- Mm.
- Greatest first date ever.
[laughs]
♪ ♪
- I don't feel like
Sydney knows me.
I can't change that
she already told him something,
and now I have to
confront that with Peter
and kind of have that, like,
scary conversation with him.
Like, I just feel like
it's just a lot.
I need to go talk to Peter,
and I need to clear this up
with him
before I'm able
to really enjoy today.
♪ ♪
Hey, you.
- Hello.
- I'm actually gonna
kidnap you somewhere...
- Okay. Let me get on my shoes.
- A little bit more intimate.
- All righty.
- My biggest fear today
is that Peter's gonna
be able to look at me
and tell me
he doesn't trust me,
he doesn't trust my heart
in this,
and that's--
that's terrifying for me,
'cause that does mean
that I could go home tonight.
You can't have a relationship
without trust.
I'm sorry it took me so long
to come grab you.
- Mm, that's okay.
- I had to kind of, you know,
face a couple of things, 'cause
obviously, last night sucked.
- Mm-hmm.
- I mean, I'm not gonna lie.
Like, that was probably
the hardest night
that I've had in a very,
very, very long time.
Like, not just here.
Just in life.
Because I've never had, like,
my authenticity
come into question, ever.
[sighs]
Like, a relationship
is nothing without trust,
and I felt last night
like you didn't trust me.
- I don't want to have doubts.
I hate this.
My biggest fear in all this
is falling for someone
and then getting to the end
and realizing
that they're not really
who they were showing me,
and I was fooled.
And I just can't
let that happen to myself.
I can't--I just--I wanna--
I have to guard my heart.
- That is a very real fear,
and it's a very valid fear,
and I--if I was in your
position,
I would be terrified
of the exact same thing,
so I understand that
completely.
- Do you see why
some of the other girls
in the house
maybe feel a fakeness from you?
Do you--do you understand
why they maybe think that?
- Not really, because like,
I choose to be happy,
and I don't know if that's--
if that's what's
coming off "disgenuine,"
'cause that's just me.
- Mm-hmm.
- Like, I feel so drawn to you,
and every time
that I look at you,
I have butterflies,
and I get so excited.
- Okay.
- Like, this feeling that I get
when I'm talking to you
and when I'm with you
and you're looking at me
like you are,
like, it's so worth it.
Like, I can't fake feelings.
I can't fake emotions.
I, like--I'm s--
I'm a horrid liar.
I am literally, like,
the world's worst liar.
- That's a good thing.
- Like, if I didn't
feel chemistry
with whoever the guy is
or if I wasn't interested,
I can't fake it.
- [inhales, sighs]
I believe you.
- Do you?
- I do.
- Do you actually?
- No, I promise you.
Like, I'm not kidding you...
- [murmurs] Oh, my goodness.
- When I say, like,
how drawn to you I am.
I just--and I know
it's so early,
but I--I don't know.
There's just something
about you that I...
I really like, and...
there's no perfection here,
okay?
I don't want that.
No perfect pageant whatever.
Here, I just wanna see Alayah
and who you are...
- I promise you
you're getting Alayah.
- And the good, the bad,
the ugly; everything.
I wanna see that.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- Thank you for reassuring me.
- Thank you for listening.
I feel so freakin' amazing
right now.
I feel back
on top of the world.
I feel like I climbed
the mountain,
I got knocked off,
and I was like,
"Uh-uh. Not today."
And I'm back on the top
of the mountain.
I was so scared
coming into that conversation
that he was gonna
want to send me home
because of something
somebody else said.
We have this undeniable
connection.
Like, that is a fact.
Future Alayah Weber,
out.
Like, I feel so much better.
What's up, bitches?
What's up, y'all?
- Girl,
how'd your conversation go?
- Amazing.
- Come over here.
- I am so happy.
- Good.
- What happened?
- Basically, I feel like we
were able to talk through it.
We had the hard conversation
we needed to have,
and we're back on track.
[soft music]
- When I talked to Alayah,
I felt good about our talk.
I have an attraction
towards her,
and I connected
from the beginning with her.
- Cheers to being
real as [bleep].
- Cheers.
- Cheers, ladies.
- With Alayah, what I think
I see is the truth,
but my logical brain says
that yes, there are flags.
Right now, I...
I'm just doing the best I can
navigating this.
- Where are we going?
- Let's go right here.
You know,
I'm still holding out that...
that love is waiting for me
at the end of this.
A little chilly
right now, huh?
I don't want anything
disingenuous about this.
I want people
'cause they want to be here
and for one reason.
I feel like your opinion...
- Mm-hmm.
- Is something
that I will take,
you know,
in the highest regard.
- Yeah.
- And I just wanted to ask you
kind of what you thought
about the stuff going on.
- Mm-hmm.
Obviously, I shared with you
that I was, like,
Miss Louisiana,
and so I did know Alayah
a little bit
before going into this.
- You did.
- I probably had spent, maybe,
like, collectively
three hours with her,
like, together,
even at Miss USA.
And it's difficult for me
to be in this position,
but I do know that she asked
that I not tell producers
that we knew one another.
And I didn't really
understand why,
um, because I was like,
"Let's not--
I don't want to lie.
I can't lie."
Um, I didn't think of it
much then,
but looking back now,
I'm like,
"Well, she did ask me to lie,"
and like, that's not who I am.
- [groans]
- And, um...
coming into this,
she was really
open to all the opportunities
that will come after this,
even if you weren't
her husband, so...
maybe she's not
the one for you.
Um...
[dramatic music]
[clears throat]
[whispers] I'm sorry.
- Hey, no.
Thank you for your honesty.
♪ ♪
- Like, I feel like
our conversation
really was...
exactly what I needed.
I feel so much [bleep]
better now.
I needed that.
- Want a belly rub?
- Yeah. Uhh.
[both giggling]
♪ ♪
- Hello.
- [high-pitched] Hi!
- Hey, mind if I--
we talk again?
- Okay, fine.
I'm coming, I'm coming.
I don't know
where my shoes are.
- All right.
- Let's go.
I'm just very much confused.
More confused than ever.
I don't have the time to waste
on someone that's not here
for me.
But I feel strongly
towards Alayah.
- Are we going back
to our spot?
- Yeah. That okay?
- I feel like this is like
a sacred spot.
This was like
our first talking spot.
- Yes, it was.
- We came through, like,
a difficult talk
in this spot.
- My heart says one thing,
but my head's screaming,
"Stop it."
I just do not want to make
the wrong decision
and be fooled.
♪ ♪
- Who is he talking to now?
- Probably still Alayah.
- Peter's all upset,
questioning who's here
for the right reasons,
and I don't know what happened
with, like, Alayah today,
but hopefully, like,
after he gets some clarity,
like, things will lighten up.
[tense music]
- I hate that--
that I, uh...
I hate that I feel
like I have to keep
bringing this kind
of stuff up with you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...
'cause I kind of just hoped
that we had squashed,
you know, it,
at the last talk we just had
earlier today.
- Yeah.
- Um...
but I just still don't feel...
100%, I guess, good about it.
Um, and...
- Okay.
- The reason I say that
is because,
uh, it's not just like one
or like two, you know, girls
that've brought stuff up.
It's been multiple people
that have kind
of brought stuff up,
and um, I just--I guess
I have some questions
that I just want just honest,
direct answers to.
- Okay.
I mean, yeah.
I'm--I promise I'll tell you
whatever you need to--
I guess I'm--I'm sorry, like...
- I'm not trying to throw you
under the bus,
but maybe you've been,
like, a little manipulative
towards some
of the other women?
- Wait. What?
- Um, like--
- I'm really confused.
Like, who--
- Did you tell Victoria...
- Uh-huh.
- To tell the producers
you guys
didn't know each other
before you came on the show?
[dramatic music]
That's what we're
talking about.
- Victoria and I are friends
outside of this.
Like, Victoria P. and I
know each other very well
outside of this environment,
and so basically,
before getting here,
my biggest fear was that
I would get disqualified
and she would get disqualified
because we knew the other
person was coming.
And I didn't want that for her,
I didn't want that for me,
and I was very scared
for both of us
that that was gonna
be an issue.
Like, that's all it was.
It wasn't me
being manipulative.
Like, I'm just shocked
that that would even
be, like,
brought up as manipulative.
Like, at the end of the day,
that's why I am here
is to get to know you.
And that is why
I didn't want, like,
this chance to get to know you
to be taken away from me.
I mean, what--
what--Peter--
- That doesn't, like--
Do not see, like, from my side,
how all I've asked
from the very beginning
is just to be open and real
and raw and truthful--
- Yes. No, I do.
- I-I've told you
so many times.
Like, I like you a lot.
Like, I--
- Okay, I know that,
and I'm being honest with you.
I'm not lying to you
about anything.
This--I mean--
- Just try to, like,
look from my perspective.
- I am, I'm trying,
but I guess--
- [stammering]
That doesn't look genuine.
Because for everything that
I've seen from Victoria so far,
like, she just seems like
she'd have no reason to lie.
And hearing that you
were trying to, like,
cover it up that you guys
knew each other and just--
- It's--no, I'm not
trying to cover up
that we know each other.
That's not at all it.
It was just, I didn't want us
to not be able to be here
because we, like, knew
the other person was doing it.
♪ ♪
- Okay.
Um...
Yeah. Yeah.
I just got a lot
to think about.
So...
- Kay.
- All right.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
[groans]
- [crying]
♪ ♪
- I just saw his face.
Like, he's not in a good place.
He's, like, really upset.
♪ ♪
- [crying]
[whispering]
I just feel weak.
[crying]
♪ ♪
- For him to have
so many questions
and just doubt
a lot of things,
it sucks to see.
- Yeah, it's not girl drama
anymore.
It's him doubting
if people are here
for the right intentions
for just him.
- Yeah.
- Hello.
I know I'm not exactly
who you wanted to see
and you were hoping Peter
was gonna be coming back,
but he is not.
He's gone home.
He's emotional,
he's confused,
and the next time he sees you,
it'll be at the Rose Ceremony.
♪ ♪
So I'll leave you.
You guys get ready
for the Rose Ceremony,
and we'll see you this evening.
[dramatic chords]
♪ ♪
- Are you okay, Mykenna?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- [sniffs]
I feel like I needed time
with him tonight,
and I didn't get it.
I don't even know--eight of us
didn't get time.
It's, like, frustrating
for so many of us.
And it doesn't even matter
if you have a rose or not.
You need that damn time
with him,
because time
is so precious here.
You don't know
what's gonna happen tonight.
Like, we could be going home
tonight,
and that's so [bleep]
frustrating.
♪ ♪
- [crying]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- I did not think that
I would be feeling this broken
going into this Rose Ceremony.
I do think that
there's a very good chance
that Peter might want
to send me home tonight.
♪ ♪
The last thing I expected
was me being called a liar
and being called manipulative
by some of the girls
in the house.
Victoria P. and I
knew each other before this.
Whatever she said to him
was enough
to really mess
with our relationship.
To hear that somebody
that I considered a friend
and an ally coming into this
was able to just slaughter
my name so quickly,
like, apparently, I can't
trust anybody in this house,
and that sucks.
♪ ♪
- I told the truth.
I just am sad
that it hurt her feelings
and that she's, like, openly,
like, and verbally
upset about it.
But I just couldn't lie.
I just had to tell the truth
to the person that I am
falling in love with.
♪ ♪
- I'm really nervous
about this Rose Ceremony.
I've had one group date.
That's it.
So it really sucks that I
didn't get time with him today.
♪ ♪
Peter was focused
on the Alayah situation.
He's getting all these doubts
into his mind,
and so now he's doubting
everyone else's relationship,
including mine.
I do not want to go home.
I want to continue
getting to know him.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
Hi, ladies.
- [quietly] Hey.
- Hi.
- This, uh--this week has--
it's definitely been
a little rough for me.
You know, there's been a lot
of amazing moments,
and you know,
I'm holding on to that,
but this has definitely
been difficult for me.
[suspenseful music]
Just being completely honest
with all of you,
I feel like
I'm more confused now.
[sighs]
I know also that
there was a lot of you
I wasn't able to spend time
with and talk to tonight,
and I'm so sorry for that.
Know that I'm doing
my absolute best with this.
This is not easy, so...
thank you for bearing with me.
♪ ♪
Kelsey.
Kelsey, will you accept
this rose?
- I will. Thank you.
♪ ♪
Hannah Ann.
Hannah Ann, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- I wasn't really involved
in the drama directly,
but I didn't get my time
with Peter today,
and this is very frustrating.
- Natasha.
♪ ♪
Natasha, will you accept
this rose?
- I will.
- I don't know what he wants
at this point,
but I know why I'm here,
and I know what I want,
and I know that's Peter.
I just hope that he feels
the same way.
- Lexi.
♪ ♪
Lexi, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- To be sent home tonight
without even having
the chance to talk to him--
I'd be heartbroken, for sure.
- Madison.
♪ ♪
Madison, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
- Like, I'm taking this
so seriously.
Like...
I don't want to go home,
especially because of drama
that has nothing to do
with me.
I'm like--I'm honestly scared.
♪ ♪
- Shiann.
Shiann, will you accept
this rose?
- Always.
Thank you.
♪ ♪
- This drama is just, like,
taking over the house.
It affected, like,
seven of us tonight
that didn't get time with him.
- Kelley.
♪ ♪
Kelley, will you accept
this rose?
- Of course.
- I think the hardest part
is that I care
so much for him.
And, like, not getting
that time with him
and seeing how upset he was,
like, it broke my heart.
- Kiarra.
♪ ♪
Kiarra, will you accept
this rose?
- I will.
- I could be going home
tonight,
and I didn't get that chance
to even express how I felt
or, like, show more of me.
He's just so caught up
in the drama,
and that sucks.
- Tammy.
Tammy, will you accept
this rose?
- Always.
- You know, getting a rose
tonight would mean that,
despite literally all
of the freaking obstacles
our relationship has faced
in the last 24 hours,
he's not ready to completely
give up on me.
- Savannah.
♪ ♪
Savannah, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes.
Thank you.
- I am being real.
These feelings are real.
I'm not being a liar or fake.
I just hope he can see that,
'cause I'm not ready
to go home yet.
♪ ♪
- Deandra.
Deandra, will you accept
this rose?
- Yes, I will.
♪ ♪
- I was drawn to Alayah,
and I wish I wasn't,
but I am,
and it--it would be so easy
to just let her go
and say bye to her,
and yet I'm still here
just torn and conflicted,
not wanting to say bye to her,
wondering, "What if she
could be my future wife?"
I'm just so confused.
♪ ♪
Like, I don't know right now.
I don't want to regret this.
- What are you gonna do?
- I don't know, man.
I--oh, [bleep].
♪ ♪
[tense music]
- [sighs]
- What are you thinking?
- I don't know, man.
I mean, uh,
I just don't know now.
♪ ♪
- So it's all coming down
to Alayah.
♪ ♪
- Yeah, I want
to give it to her so bad,
but I just do not want
to regret this.
- How much do you think
you'll regret it
if you send her home tonight?
♪ ♪
- I don't know, uh...
I was hoping, like,
I'd feel, like,
some type of for-sure-ness
being up there,
and I didn't.
♪ ♪
Okay.
- Okay.
♪ ♪
- [long exhale]
I'm sorry for that.
♪ ♪
- Ladies, sorry
for the interruption,
but there's been a little bit
of a change tonight.
♪ ♪
This is now the final rose
tonight.
When you're ready.
♪ ♪
- I don't want him
to give up on me yet.
♪ ♪
I have so much to give
and so much to offer.
♪ ♪
And I just would hate for him
to, like, miss out
on the opportunity
to get to know who I am.
That's just what breaks
my heart the most.
♪ ♪
Mykenna.
Mykenna, will you accept
this rose?
- Always. Yes.
Of course.
♪ ♪
- Ladies, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment
to say your goodbyes.
- [quietly]
Bye, guys.
- Bye.
- It's okay.
♪ ♪
- Jasmine, I'm sorry.
- Hey.
- No, it's fine.
- I mean, I'm just, like,
so happy
that Alayah is going home.
I saw it from day one.
She's fake.
I stand by what I said,
and I'm never gonna go back
on my opinion of someone.
- Bye, ladies.
- And I'm proud of Peter
for making a stand
and going with his gut.
♪ ♪
- [quietly]
I'm sorry.
- [breathes deeply]
I'm sorry too.
- [sighs]
This was not easy for me
at all.
♪ ♪
- I mean, I can't say
I'm not disappointed
that I didn't get a chance
to prove you different,
but if it's your choice,
then I'm gonna respect
your choice.
Okay.
- All right.
- Good luck.
- Thanks.
♪ ♪
[sighs]
Bye.
- Bye.
♪ ♪
- I love you.
- Love you.
- Love you guys.
♪ ♪
Like, I'm disappointed.
Didn't at all end
how I expected,
and it just sucks
that I am going out
because of other people's
opinions
and not what he saw
directly from me.
♪ ♪
That's the hardest part.
[sniffs, sighs]
I'm not gonna hold a grudge
against Victoria,
but you know,
at the end of the day,
her comments to Peter
are, I really believe,
the reason that I'm going home
right now.
I mean,
I guess I'll always wonder
if that rose that Chris
took away was for me.
♪ ♪
- That was tough.
This is getting hard,
but I am just gonna
follow my heart
and keep doing that, so...
here's to next week,
and let's just keep this going.
- Bye, Peter.
- All right, we'll see you.
Bye.
- That hurt bad.
Even though today
was difficult,
I think Peter is taking
what everyone has to say
very seriously.
He really looked like
he was in pain.
But I'm falling
in love with him,
and I'm gonna continue
to put him first
and our relationship first
and speak the truth
even when it's difficult.
Like, I don't feel good
right now.
I don't feel good.
- No?
Like, I thought I would.
I don't feel good.
♪ ♪
- I think I just, like,
gave in
to just listening
to everyone else,
to be completely honest.
- He was clearly, like,
distraught today.
- He was.
- I just--I don't want it--
I don't want this drama
to keep carrying on,
you know what I mean?
It's affecting so many of us,
and like--
- This is so hard for him,
and it's just getting
harder and harder, you know?
♪ ♪
- I feel like I'm gonna
regret this like crazy,
and I'm not gonna, like,
get past this for a while.
Like, I...
[sighs]
♪ ♪
Like, I thought that
that was the right
thing to do,
but like,
I don't know right now.
[sighs]
I just hope I made
the right decision.
♪ ♪
- Coming up next week
on "The Bachelor"...
[cheers]
- It's a fresh start.
It's a new week.
Peter and I have
the strongest connection.
I'm so excited!
- Oh, yeah.
- I think that we're falling
in love with one another.
- I have a surprise
for Victoria.
We have our own private
Chase Rice concert.
- Oh, my God.
[dramatic music]
- Chase and I dated.
- What?
- [crying]
I can't do this.
- Tonight, there's 13 of us,
so I'm gonna be tackling girls
to get time with Peter tonight.
- [gasps]
- Shut the...
both: Front door.
- Drama has risen
from the dead.
- I'm here to freaking
set the record straight
about what was said about me.
- I'm obviously
being lied to by someone.
- She's manipulating you
the same way
that she manipulated me.
- It was like the biggest
slap in the face.
Like, I couldn't even
look at you.
- I'm gonna go.
- [gasps]
- It's all coming up
next week
on "The Bachelor."
[bull roaring]
- Oh, boy.
- Peter's about to ride
the bull!
[women cheering]
- All right.
Let's do this.
- Let's go!
Wait. Can I control it?
- Don't go easy.
Let's go.
There we go.
Whoo!
All right,
let's go, cowgirl.
- I don't know
what I'm doing.
- You don't know
what you're doing?
Oh, I'm scared.
[people chanting]
Ride that bull!
- Ready.
[bluegrass music]
Whoo!
Oh, yeah!
♪ ♪
- Wait.
- Harder!
♪ ♪
Oh, [bleep].
Oh, [bleep]!
Whoo! Whoo!
Whoo! Ooh! Oh!
Oh, [bleep].
Oh, damn.
Ow.
- Okay.
- Ow, ow.
Oh, my God. I'm dizzy.
- Don't throw up.
[people chanting]
Ride that bull!
- Nothing to see here, guys.